[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "What do we actually know about what happened here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "We're learning, actually, a little bit more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Do we think he had a very specific set of targets or was he stopped from being more indiscriminate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Very specific targets.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "And did they have any armed security at the school?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "This is a very interesting point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Gabby"]}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "What did you think when you heard another school shooting today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Well, you know, just like you, Piers, I often think about what happened to Gabby.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "You know, I was optimistic that after today's meeting in the White House that there would be, you know, some statement that they could find some common ground.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "So your solution if you were there in that meeting would be to arm every school, every church, every hospital, everywhere that members of the public could be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "You certainly would want to encourage people who are qualified to carry a concealed firearm to be able to do so in a school zone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jared Loughner"], "LOCATION": ["Gabby"]}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "VBN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "You know, how many -- I mean, where does it -- where does it end?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Also, I mean, if you go back to what happened to Gabby on that day, there was somebody legally armed, a 24-year-old man, and he didn't actually in the end tackle Jared Loughner.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Walgreens", "Safeway"]}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "I mean, is that helpful in that situation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Well, there was a man in a Walgreens next to the Safeway that came out when he heard the shooting, pulled out his firearm, and nearly shot the man who was involved in taking down the gunman.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "What do you think of people in that position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Well, certainly, there are a lot of options.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "What is your message to the NRA?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Well, you know, I'd like to be able to sit down with the NRA at some point and talk to them about this.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "So why am I off the rails, Mr. Shapiro?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "You know, honestly, Piers, you've kind of been a bully on this issue because what you do, and I've seen it repeatedly on your show, I watch your show, and I have seen it repeatedly.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Shapiro"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "How dare you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "I have seen you do it repeatedly, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Like I say, how dare you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "I mean, you can keep saying that, but you've done it repeatedly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Let me ask you --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "So you only care about the kids who were being killed in Chicago as much as the kids in Sandy Hook?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "And why don't you care about -- about banning the handguns in Chicago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", ":", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "We'll come to that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "What was the weapon used in Aurora in the movie theater?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "It was -- it was an assault rifle, sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Aurora"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "What was the weapon used in the Oregon shopping mall?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "I believe it's an assault weapon, correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oregon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "What was the weapon used in Sandy Hook?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "It was an assault rifle.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Why is it here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Well, you know, we can talk about Britain in a second.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["next 50"]}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Which tyranny are you fearing yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "I fear the possibility of a tyranny rising in this country in the next 50 to 100 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Is that your position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "And that's not my position.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", ":", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "What is your position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "My position is that we have to calibrate laws that are designed to get hand -- guns out of the hands of bad people and keep guns in the hands of good people who want to buy them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "JJR", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "How do you do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "I think one of the ways that you do that is by better screening for mental illness.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "Was Adam Lanza's mother a good person?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "I don't know whether she's a good person or a bad person.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam Lanza"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Has there been any evidence to suggest she was not a good person?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "No, but there is --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 370, "question": "ORGAN: Then she becomes a bad person, does she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Well, no, it's not a matter of -- it's not a matter of morally versus immorally --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "So is she good or bad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "You're right, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "So she goes from good to bad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Do you believe that if you had an assault weapon ban, statistics prove that you could dry out the supply of these guns and make them less accessible to criminals?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "I don't know whether you could make them less accessible to criminals.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NNPS", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Why just stop yourself at assault rifles?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "Because I believe and respect an Americans' rights under the Second Amendment Constitution that you kindly brought in to defend themselves with a handgun or a pistol.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "PRP", "DT", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "If he hadn't had the assault rifle, he wouldn't have used them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "Explain to me this: I can't buy this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Do you think that's right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Well, we can talk drug laws another time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Does that make sense to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VB", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "No, I think what would make sense is laws that are calibrated to solve the problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Which guns would you remove?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "I think the ones that have largely been removed from the market.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "You wouldn't remove any semiautomatics at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "No, because semiautomatic just means that when you pull the trigger once, one bullet comes out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Do you understand how an AR-15 performs when it's been modified and has a magazine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Would you want every American to have an AR-15?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "No, not every American.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Who would you stop?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "I would stop anyone with a criminal background.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "For everybody?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "For everybody.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "So there should be a database, a national registry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "If it's not public.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "When the NRA came out today, after the meeting in the White House, and just said we're not prepared to entertain any kind of new gun restrictions, what did you think about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "What is astonishing to me is the left's attack on the NRA.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA", "White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "They instill fear?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "If everyone in the movie theater had been armed, everyone in the school had been armed, it wouldn't have happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ronald Reagan"]}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Why did Ronald Reagan want these assault weapons removed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "You know, I don't know why Ronald Reagan wanted these --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ronald Reagan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Reagan"]}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "You like Reagan, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "I like Reagan.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Reagan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "Did you agree with him on assault weapons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "If -- I'll believe what you are saying, sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Why don't you tell me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Let me read the letter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Do you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "I have been debating this for a very long time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "Why do they need those weapons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "They need them for the prospective possibility of resistance to tyranny, which is not a concern today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Where do you expect the tyranny to come from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "It could come from the United States, because governments have gone tyrannical before, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Do you understand how absurd you sound?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "Here's where you go into the absurd and the bullying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sandy Hook"]}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "What is astonishing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "What's astonishing about it is that for weeks now, you have been saying that anybody who disagrees with your position is absurd, idiotic, and doesn't care about the kids in Sandy Hook.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ":", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Let me ask you again, what is the point of a civilian having an AR-15?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "The point of a civilian having an AR-15 assault weapon -- many of them are ex-military.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "An average civilian without a criminal record, why do they need one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "To protect against the possibility of eventual government tyranny.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Is that what you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "They may not turn on me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "The reason we cannot remove AR-15 assault weapons is because the threat of your own government turning on you in a tyrannical way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "-NONE-", "NN", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "That is your position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "It is because there are countervailing rights and responsibilities.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "What would you need a fully automatic weapon for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Or the semiautomatic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "What advice can you give them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "Hang in there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "Have you thought about going up to Sandy Hook?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "I would love to go up to Sandy Hook.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 744, "question": "How many young females have done this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 745, "answer": "Almost all the recent massacres have been young males.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]